Punishment used to be eye for an eye.
Someone killed your nephew, and you got to kill their nephew.
And it worked!
Then some ancient hipster came up with "prisons"
And that fad never died.
The problem with them is that anyone can escape as long as they have
one cool rebel and a fun planning montage.
So today I'm gonna show you how to make a prison unescapable.
Inescapable?
Not scapable?
Here it is, 27 prisoners. Hasn't permanently been 27.
Several died in riots related to laundry.
About 10 had to die before I bought a washing machine.
Other than extremely deadly riots, very safe prison.
Hosting people guilty of, uh.....VIDEO GAME PIRACY?!? *pffffffffffff*
I spat out my coffee... Might have been a better visual gag.
I didn't know we had such sick fucks in my prison.We need armed guards.
To combat torrenters I have this and my new favorite room...
THE EXECUTION ROOM.
Always so gloomy in movies. I didn't want that. I have couches, and of course a snack machine.
So people can relax and enjoy.
Most prisoners are cool though, like this guy who's guilty of... Necrophilia.
What's that? Is that like a necromancer? We can't hold that! We need more security!
BEHOLD, the safest prison in the galaxy. 40 sniper towers, a moat filled with starved killer whales, and on top of it all, I have banned rebels and planning montages!
I've made piles and piles of money, but how can I be so rich when I'm in the red?
That's tax evasion 101 mate! Always lose money! And you can't get caught!
What are you gonna do? Put a prison owner in prison? That's literally against the laws of physics!
*random stuff happens and epic fight music plays whilst Kilian is arguing about the fact that "is mere game" and "it's medicinal!"*
The trial did not go great...
My lawyer expected me to get 3 to 5 years, but uh... I'm on death row!
So I really, really need to escape this place. There is one way to get out of being roasted.
Laundry. Stealing clothes.
I saved money by not keeping any records and instead judged people based on the way they dress.
Sadly, it will be impossible for me to get out of here. My guards are the best in the world, the absolute elite.
Y... yo.. you.. you.. you forgot to close the door.
Uuuuuugggghhhh......
Wow, NO ONE IS STOPPING ME! I should have fired all of you. They will notice someone is gone.
Good thing Jared looks exactly like me.
Let's frame him!
If you feel bad don't worry about it, they'll let him go the second he explains he's in for jaywalking.
*ZAP*
I still need a plan how to get out of here. I've seen every escape movie ever made. Even the best one of them all, Escape Plan.
And if Stallone can escape in 90 minutes, I can do it in 10.
I ain't got shit.
Everything I come up with is impossible to do without a planning montage.
I have made some friends though.
Obviously Will the Necrophile. Andre, He's the leader and sole member of this prison's Aryan alliance. No, I don't know if he knows.
There's also Timmy, Frank and Mr. GruntelSkoppi.
I've also made a big enemy. Turns out, Jared's dad is the leader of the Yakuza. Apparently, he's going to kill me tonight after I brush my teeth. Therefore we need to escape right now.
And because we can't plan, we gotta improvise.
Frank's gonna dig a tunnel, Will is gonna go get whale poison from the infirmary, specifically the one next to the morgue for some reason, the rest of us are gonna kill Jared's dad.
First get a distraction. A simple little thing that will get the guards' attention.
OH... OH NO!
They slaughtered Andre and the place is on fire, let's-let's just stick to the thing.. THERE HE IS!
Yes! We did it, let's get to the tunnel!
*collapse noise*
What just happened? The tunnel collapsed? Frank's dead?!
OK, new idea! Let's force our way out.
Place is on lockdown. We are dead men.
'father had a tunnel? We're saved!... NOPE, led us to the laundry.
Apparently, daddy likes to sniff detergent.
It's next to the armory though. Maybe we can get in and grab some weapons!
YOU CAN'T PUNCH OPEN IRON BARS! I stand corrected.
Shouldn't have entered this place.
With 3 people we can still do this though. TIMMY JUST RAN FOR IT!
WHAT THE SHIT!?
Whatever! Go to the infirmary and meet up with my favorite undead summoner.
WHERE IS HE!? WHERE IS ANYBODY!?
THEY GOT HIM! Fuck this. I'm gonna try and mail myself out.
Wait, Timmy did it! You can do it! I believe in yo... OK.
All of my friends are dead.
And now I am alone.
Waiting here until I die.
Except no,that's not me.That's Killian with 2 L's. I already left.
Because there are no rules against explaining montages.
It started by making Frank dig a way longer tunnel than we needed. Then I told Andre to punch the leader of the biggest prison gang, the Ebony Panthers, causing a distracting and confusing riot. Jared's dad actually hated his jaywalking son; who wouldn't? And told me of his escape tunnel.
But only I get to escape so he had to die. Meanwhile, Frank would dig to the moat with the starved whales, turning them into full and sleepy whales. We reached the new section with its armory. I would personally never hurt my employees but I need to hurt my camera monitors.
With only 3 alive, I told Timmy had given up and he should run for it. In reality, I had a doctors' appointment. I knew what necrophilia is so I knew all the doctors would be busy trying to pull him away, meaning the infirmary would be empty.
With a sewer that connects to the mail room next to the lawyers' office. MY lawyers' office, the only place not protected by the wall. There was still had a huge sniper problem.
Good thing that in 3, 2, 1, he'll be distracted. And that is the Prison Escape Experience.
*outro music plays*